Guide to the National Education Association-Conventions records, 1857-1998 NEA1008.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Conventions and Conferences, Bulk, 1970-1996 1858-1998; 1970-1996; Series 1; National Education Association of the United States. Meeting.; 85 Linear Feet
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Resolutions, Series 1 (Box 1470, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Resolutions Meeting, Series 1 (Box 1470, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-San Francisco Convention Bureau [file 1/2], 1989-1993; Series 1 (Box 1470, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-San Francisco Convention Bureau [file 2/2], 1989-1993; Series 1 (Box 1471, Folder 1)
    Contains a button.
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Schedules, Series 1 (Box 1471, Folder 2)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Site Booklet, Series 1 (Box 1471, Folder 3)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Socials, Series 1 (Box 1471, Folder 4)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Staff, Series 1 (Box 1471, Folder 5)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-State Coordinators [file 1/2], 1990-1993; Series 1 (Box 1471, Folder 6)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-State Coordinators [file 2/2], 1990-1993; Series 1 (Box 1471, Folder 7)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Tours, 1991-1992; Series 1 (Box 1471, Folder 8)
  - 1993-San Francisco, CA-Yerba Buena Gardens, 1991-1993; Series 1 (Box 1471, Folder 9)
  - 1994 NEA National Conference Series: The New learning Environment Serving Diversity Through Technology, April 1994; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 21)
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Clinton, Hillary, Series 1 (Box 1472, Folder 1)
    Clinton, Hillary
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1993-1994; Series 1 (Box 1472, Folder 2)
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Delegate Packets, Series 1 (Box 1472, Folder 3)
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Exhibit Information, 1991-1994; Series 1 (Box 1472, Folder 4)
  - 1994- New Orleans, LA- Financial Reports: Secretary- Treasurer Independent Auditors, July 1994; Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 5)
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Furniture Orders, Series 1 (Box 1472, Folder 5)
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Pre-Conference Meetings, 1993-1994; Series 1 (Box 1472, Folder 6)
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Program/Platform Guests, 1993-1994; Series 1 (Box 1472, Folder 7)
  - 1994- New Orleans, LA- Public Education is a Public Trust- 132nd Annual Meeting, July 1-6, 1994; Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 6)
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Schedules, Series 1 (Box 1472, Folder 8)
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Script [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1472, Folder 9)
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Script [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1473, Folder 1)
  - 1994-New Orleans, LA-Socials, 1993-1994; Series 1 (Box 1473, Folder 2)
  - 1995 Annual Meeting, series 1 (Box 4379, Folder 8)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Busing, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1473, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Contracts [file 1/3], 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1473, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Contracts [file 2/3], 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1473, Folder 5)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Contracts [file 3/3], 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1473, Folder 6)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Convention Bureau [file 1/2], 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1474, Folder 1)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Convention Bureau [file 2/2], 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1474, Folder 2)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Convention Center, Series 1 (Box 1474, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Correspondence-Miscellaneous, Series 1 (Box 1474, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Delegate Packets, Series 1 (Box 1474, Folder 5)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Event Documents [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1474, Folder 6)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Event Documents [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1474, Folder 7)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Exhibits [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1475, Folder 1)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Exhibits [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1475, Folder 2)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Folder, Series 1 (Box 1475, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Friend of Education Committee, Series 1 (Box 1475, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Gore, Al, Series 1 (Box 1475, Folder 5)
    Gore, Albert
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Host Committee, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1475, Folder 6)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Airport Hilton, Series 1 (Box 1475, Folder 7)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Comfort Inn-Bloomington, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1475, Folder 8)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Crown Sterling Suites-Airport, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1476, Folder 1)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Crown Sterling Suites-Downtown, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1476, Folder 2)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Crown Sterling Suites-St. Paul, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1476, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Embassy Suites Airport, Series 1 (Box 1476, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Airport 2, Series 1 (Box 1476, Folder 5)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Bloomington Central, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1476, Folder 6)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Holiday Inn-International Airport, Series 1 (Box 1476, Folder 7)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Metrodome, Series 1 (Box 1476, Folder 8)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Minneapolis West, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1477, Folder 1)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Hotel Luxeford, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1477, Folder 2)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Hotel Sofitel, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1477, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Hyatt Regency, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1477, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Marquette Hotel, Series 1 (Box 1477, Folder 5)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Marriott Airport, Series 1 (Box 1477, Folder 6)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Marriott City Center, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1477, Folder 7)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Marriott Southwest, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1477, Folder 8)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Minneapolis Athletic Club, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1478, Folder 1)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Minneapolis Hilton and Towers, 1991-1995; Series 1 (Box 1478, Folder 2)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Normandy, Series 1 (Box 1478, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Northland Inn, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1478, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Omni Northstar, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1478, Folder 5)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Park Inn International, Series 1 (Box 1478, Folder 6)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Radisson-Metrodome, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1478, Folder 7)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Radisson-Plaza, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1478, Folder 8)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Radisson-St. Paul, 1993; Series 1 (Box 1478, Folder 9)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Radisson Hotel and Conference Center, 1993; Series 1 (Box 1479, Folder 1)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Radisson Hotel South and Plaza Tower, Series 1 (Box 1479, Folder 2)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Ramada-Minneapolis West, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1479, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Registry Hotel, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1479, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-St. Paul Hotel, Series 1 (Box 1479, Folder 5)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Sheraton-Airport, 1993; Series 1 (Box 1479, Folder 6)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Sheraton Inn Midway, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1479, Folder 7)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Sheraton Metrodome, 1993; Series 1 (Box 1479, Folder 8)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Sheraton Park Place, 1993-1995; Series 1 (Box 1479, Folder 9)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Thunderbird, Series 1 (Box 1479, Folder 10)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Turned Down Hotels, 1993; Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 1)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Hotels-Wyndham Garden, Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 2)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Incident Report, Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Meeting Room Requests, Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Miscellaneous, Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 5)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-NCUEA, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 6)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Permit Occupancy, 1994; Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 7)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Pre-Convention Meeting, Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 8)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-President's Script, Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 9)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Program/Platform Guests, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 10)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Programs [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 11)
    Contains 4 copies.
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Programs [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1480, Folder 12)
  - 1995- Minneapolis, MN- Public Education Works for America- 133rd Annual Meeting, July 1-6, 1995; Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 7)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-"R.A. Today" [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1481, Folder 1)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-"R.A. Today" [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1481, Folder 2)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Resolutions Committee, Series 1 (Box 1481, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Schedules, Series 1 (Box 1481, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Site Visit, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1481, Folder 5)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Socials, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 1)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Special Activities, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 2)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Student Program, 1994-1995; Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Tour, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Minneapolis, MN-Visitor's Guides, 1992-1995; Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 5)
  - 1996 National Education Summit Directory of Business Leaders, series 1 (Box 4379, Folder 9)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Board Steering Committee, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 6)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-1st Business Session, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 7)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-2nd Business Session, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 8)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Clinton, Bill, 1995-1996; Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 9)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Constitution and Bylaws Committee, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 10)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Correspondence, 1995-1996; Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 11)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Delegate Mailing, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 12)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Elections, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 13)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Equity and Ethnic Harmony, 1995-1996; Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 14)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Exhibits, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 15)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Miscellaneous, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 16)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-NBI Committee, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 17)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Pre-R.A. Conferences, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 18)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Program, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 19)
  - 1996- Washington, DC- Public Education Achieving America's Potential- 134th Annual Meeting, June 30- July 5, 1996; Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 8)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-R.A. Program, Series 1 (Box 1482, Folder 20)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-"R.A. Today", Series 1 (Box 1483, Folder 1)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Schedule, Series 1 (Box 1483, Folder 2)
  - 1996-Washington, DC-Special Guests, Series 1 (Box 1483, Folder 3)
  - 1997- Atlanta, GA- America's Children, America's Promise- 135th Annual Meeting, July 1-6, 1997; Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 9)
  - 1997- Atlanta, GA- Annual Meeting- Security in Atlanta, Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 10)
  - 1997- Atlanta, GA- Help Us Leave Atlanta a Little Better Place; Support NEA's 'Green Eggs and Hamlet' Read-In at the 1997 RA, Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 11)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Candidates, Series 1 (Box 1483, Folder 4)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Committee on Constitution, Bylaws and Rules, Series 1 (Box 1483, Folder 5)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Correspondence-Miscellaneous, Series 1 (Box 1483, Folder 6)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Cruise, Carolyn, Series 1; Cruise, Carolyn (Box 1483, Folder 7)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Delegate Mailing, Series 1 (Box 1484, Folder 1)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Delegate Packets, Series 1 (Box 1484, Folder 2)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Platform/Program Guests, Series 1 (Box 1484, Folder 3)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Pre-Convention Meetings, 1996-1997; Series 1 (Box 1484, Folder 4)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Programs [file 1/5], Series 1 (Box 1484, Folder 5)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Programs [file 2/5], Series 1 (Box 1484, Folder 6)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Programs [file 3/5], Series 1 (Box 1484, Folder 7)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Programs [file 4/5], Series 1 (Box 1485, Folder 1)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Programs [file 5/5], Series 1 (Box 1485, Folder 2)
    Contains 3 copies.
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-"R.A. Today" [file 1/3], Series 1 (Box 1485, Folder 3)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-"R.A. Today" [file 2/3], Series 1 (Box 1485, Folder 4)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-"R.A. Today" [file 3/3], Series 1 (Box 1485, Folder 5)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Schedules, Series 1 (Box 1486, Folder 1)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Script, Series 1 (Box 1486, Folder 2)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Socials, Series 1 (Box 1486, Folder 3)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Special Activities, Series 1 (Box 1486, Folder 4)
  - 1997-Atlanta, GA-Staffing/Logistics, Series 1 (Box 1486, Folder 5)
  - 1998 Education International World Congress, July 1998; series 1 (Box 4398, Folder 30)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Camden Education Association, Series 1 (Box 1487, Folder 1)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Candidates, Series 1 (Box 1487, Folder 2)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Committee on Constitution, Bylaws and Rules, Series 1 (Box 1487, Folder 3)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Correspondence-Miscellaneous, Series 1 (Box 1487, Folder 4)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Cruise, Carolyn, Series 1 (Box 1487, Folder 5)
    Cruise, Carolyn
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Delegate Packets, 1997-1998; Series 1 (Box 1487, Folder 6)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Gore Visit, Series 1 (Box 1487, Folder 7)
    Contains a 3.5" hard disk entitled "RA Stuff, Gore Visit, Memb. Script".
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Preconvention Meetings, 1997-1998; Series 1 (Box 1487, Folder 8)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Program/Platform Guests, Series 1 (Box 1487, Folder 9)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Representative Assembly, 1993-1994; Series 1 (Box 1488, Folder 1)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-"R.A. Today", Series 1 (Box 1488, Folder 2)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Resolutions Committee, Series 1 (Box 1488, Folder 3)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Schedules, 1997-1998; Series 1 (Box 1488, Folder 4)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Script, Series 1 (Box 1488, Folder 5)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Socials, Series 1 (Box 1488, Folder 6)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Special Activities, Series 1 (Box 1488, Folder 7)
  - 1998-New Orleans, LA-Staffing/Logistics, 1997; Series 1 (Box 1488, Folder 8)
  - The 2003 NEA Fund for Children and Public Education RA Contribution Envelope Book, Series (Box 4832, Folder 12)
  - 2008 Representative Assembly, Washington DC: July 4th Celebration Featuring NEA Choir and 2008 Friend of Education Barbara Morgan, Series 1 (Box 5035, Folder 4)
  - Addresses & Proceedings: Constitutional Convention of the NEA (Volume I) [1/3], 1971; Series 1 (Box 4055, Folder 1)
  - Addresses & Proceedings: Constitutional Convention of the NEA (Volume I) [2/3], 1971; Series 1 (Box 4055, Folder 2)
  - Addresses & Proceedings: Constitutional Convention of the NEA (Volume I) [3/3], 1971; Series 1 (Box 4055, Folder 3)
  - Addresses & Proceedings: Constitutional Convention of the NEA (Volume II) [1/3], 1971; Series 1 (Box 4055, Folder 4)
  - Addresses & Proceedings: Constitutional Convention of the NEA (Volume II) [2/3], 1971; Series 1 (Box 4055, Folder 5)
  - Addresses & Proceedings: Constitutional Convention of the NEA (Volume II) [3/3], 1971; Series 1 (Box 4055, Folder 6)
  - Addresses & Proceedings: Constitutional Convention of the NEA (Volume III) [1/2], 1971; Series 1 (Box 4055, Folder 7)
  - Addresses & Proceedings: Constitutional Convention of the NEA (Volume III) [2/2], 1971; Series 1 (Box 4055, Folder 8)
  - Addresses and Proceedings of the Sixty-Third Annual Meeting Held at Indianapolis, Indiana - Minutes of the Fifth Representative Assembly, 1925; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 22)
  - Advocacy, Professionalism, and Partnerships: Pathways to Excellence, 1999 January 29-31; Series 1 (Box 4988, Folder 1)
  - Affiliate Services Meeting (1987), 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1488, Folder 9)
  - Affiliate Services Meeting/Cluster Training Meeting, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1489, Folder 1)
  - Affiliate Services Meeting/Cluster Training Meeting (1991) [file 1/2], 1989; Series 1 (Box 1489, Folder 2)
  - Affiliate Services Meeting/Cluster Training Meeting (1991) [file 2/2], 1989; Series 1 (Box 1489, Folder 3)
  - Affiliate Services Meeting/Cluster Training Meeting [file 1/2], 1990; Series 1 (Box 1489, Folder 4)
  - Affiliate Services Meeting/Cluster Training Meeting [file 2/2], 1990; Series 1 (Box 1489, Folder 5)
  - AG's Meeting, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1490, Folder 1)
  - Analysis of the Documents Developed at the July 1971 Constitutional Convention, February 1972; Series 1 (Box 4057, Folder 6)
  - Articles, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1490, Folder 2)
  - Assistant Regional Directors Meeting (1990), Series 1 (Box 1490, Folder 3)
  - Associated Exhibitors of the National Education Association Present Their Thirty-Seventh Annual Program To The Convention of AASA, 1963; Series 1 (Box 4933, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic City...Welcomes NEA, June 1972; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 23)
  - Awards for the Advancement of Learning Through Broadcasting, July 1, 1991; Series 1 (Box 4074, Folder 6)
  - Backup Correspondence, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1490, Folder 4)
  - Badges and Buttons, 1884-2007; Series 1 (Box 3318, Folder 8)
  - Black Caucus Report, June 23-July 3, 1971; Series 1 (Box 4056, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors Meeting (1989-1990) [file 1/2], 1988; Series 1 (Box 1490, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors Meeting (1989-1990) [file 2/2], 1988; Series 1 (Box 1490, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors Meeting [file 1/3], 1988-1991; Series 1 (Box 1490, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Meeting [file 2/3], 1988-1991; Series 1 (Box 1490, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors Meeting [file 3/3], 1988-1991; Series 1 (Box 1490, Folder 9)
  - Boston Marriott Copley Place Materials, 2003; Series 1 (Box 4657, Folder 4)
  - Broadcast Services, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1490, Folder 10)
  - Business Managers Meetings, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 1)
  - Candidates for NEA Officers and Executive Committee, 2000; Series 1 (Box 4988, Folder 2)
  - Celebrities Night and Golden Key Awards, 1957; Series 1 (Box 4933, Folder 4)
  - [Certificate for Workshop Participants], 2003; Series 1 (Box 4657, Folder 5)
  - CHCI 2010 Public Policy Conference: Celebrating History, Heritage, and the American Dream, 2010 September 12 - 14; Series 1 (Box 5035, Folder 5)
  - Choice Intergroup Meeting (1990), Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Lobby for a U.S. /Soviet Nuclear Weapons Freeze, undated; series 1 (Box 4418, Folder 24)
  - Conflict, Communication, and Colleagues- SEE Conference, 2003; Series 1 (Box 4657, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-1973 Proceedings and Official Minutes, March 1974; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-Advertisement for the Papers and Discussions of the International Congresses of Education, circa 1894; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 4)
  - Conventions-Attendees at the 6th Representative Assembly, 1926; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 5)
  - Conventions-"Asbestos in Our Schools", circa 1985; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-Biographical Sketches, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 7)
  - Conventions-Budgets (Cumulative), 1957-1970; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 8)
  - Conventions-Business Study, 1968; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 9)
  - Conventions-"Classified Bibliography of Topics, 1857-1906", 1907; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 10)
  - Conventions-Comments and Recommendations, 1960; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 11)
  - Conventions-"Cost Implications for New Business Items 10-31", circa 1995; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 12)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1969; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 13)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1972; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 14)
    Contained an audio cassette titled, "NEA Convention Highlights, 1972", which has been removed and placed in the Media Materials series.
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet [file 1/2], 1973; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 15)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet [file 2/2], 1973; Series 1 (Box 1491, Folder 16)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet [file 1/2], 1974; Series 1 (Box 1492, Folder 1)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet [file 2/2], 1974; Series 1 (Box 1492, Folder 2)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1976; Series 1 (Box 1492, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1977; Series 1 (Box 1492, Folder 4)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1978; Series 1 (Box 1492, Folder 5)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1979; Series 1 (Box 1492, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1980; Series 1 (Box 1492, Folder 7)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1981; Series 1 (Box 1493, Folder 1)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet [file 1/2], 1982; Series 1 (Box 1493, Folder 2)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet [file 2/2], 1982; Series 1 (Box 1493, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1983; Series 1 (Box 1493, Folder 4)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1493, Folder 5)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1493, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1494, Folder 1)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1494, Folder 2)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1494, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-Delegate Packet, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1494, Folder 4)
  - Conventions-Delegate Seating, 1959-1968; Series 1 (Box 1494, Folder 5)
  - Conventions-Digest, 1943-1947; Series 1 (Box 1494, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-Digest, 1948-1950; Series 1 (Box 1494, Folder 7)
  - Conventions-Digest, 1951-1952; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 1)
  - Conventions-Digest, 1953; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 2)
  - Conventions-Elections Committee, 1959-1970; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-Evaluation, 1953-1967; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 4)
  - Conventions-Exhibits (NEA Unit), 1963-1968; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 5)
  - Conventions-"Family Viewing", circa 1985; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-"Fiftieth Anniversary Volume" (Xeroxes), 1907; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 7)
  - Conventions-Gallup Survey on Education, July 1985; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 8)
  - Conventions-Greenblat, Arleigh, 1968; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 9)
    Greenblat, Arleigh
  - Conventions-Guides, 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 10)
  - Conventions-"Implementing the NEA Action Plan on Educational Excellence", June 1985; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 11)
  - Conventions-Indexes, 1943-1944; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 12)
  - Conventions-"Information Bulletin", 1960; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 13)
  - Conventions-"A Look at the Present", April 1986; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 14)
  - Conventions-"The Mastery in Learning Project", June 1985; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 15)
  - Conventions-Meeting Transcripts, 1922; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 16)
  - Conventions-Music, 1961-1970; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 17)
  - Conventions-NEA Fact Sheet, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 18)
  - Conventions-NEA Human and Civil Rights Awards, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 19)
  - Conventions-"National Foundation for the Improvement of Education", 1986; Series 1 (Box 1495, Folder 20)
  - Conventions-News and Notes, 1977-1979; Series 1 (Box 1496, Folder 1)
  - Conventions-News and Notes, 1980-1985; Series 1 (Box 1496, Folder 2)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1921; Series 1 (Box 1496, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1957-1967; Series 1 (Box 1496, Folder 4)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1968; Series 1 (Box 1496, Folder 5)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1969; Series 1 (Box 1496, Folder 6)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1971; Series 1 (Box 1496, Folder 7)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1972-1973; Series 1 (Box 1496, Folder 8)
  - Conventions-News Coverage, 1974; Series 1 (Box 1497, Folder 1)
  - Conventions-News Coverage [file 1/3], 1977; Series 1 (Box 1497, Folder 2)
  - Conventions-News Coverage [file 2/3], 1977; Series 1 (Box 1497, Folder 3)
  - Conventions-News Coverage [file 3/3], 1977; Series 1 (Box 1497, Folder 4)